<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>jonwin.se</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on jonwin.se</description>
    <image>
      <title>jonwin.se</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/round_logo.png</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/round_logo.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.125.4</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:05:48 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hyprland on NixOS a complete guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hl-nixos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:05:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hl-nixos/</guid>
      <description>Basic Config programs.hyprland = { enable = true; xwayland = { enable = true; }; }; Hyprland Waybar Rofi Kitty Screenshot Clipboard </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/keyboard/</guid>
      <description>I am planing to build a custom split, ergonomic, ortholinear, curved keyboard like the dactyl manuform or charybdis. My keyboard has been configured with the beta version of the Cosmos keyboard configurator found here. I will update this page as my plans change and when I have built it.
Configuration Right half Left half Components 2 Pro Micro USB-C Controller 62 Kailh Choc Switches 60 1u Kailh Choc Keycaps 2 1u Homing Kailh Choc Keycaps Cirque 40 mm Trackpad Wire for Trackpad OLED 0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWM (Dynamic Window Manager)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/dwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:40:11 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/dwm/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;dwm is an extremely fast, small, and dynamic window manager for X.&amp;rdquo; - suckless.org
This post talks about my dwm configuration and the changes I have made to it. I have installed quite a few patches and made some modifications of my own, I have also added a flake.nix to make installation on NixOS really simple. You can view the source code in my GitHub repository here.
Patches Below is a list of all the patches I have installed with a short explanation of each patch, click the links to view the patches on suckless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Layouts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/keyboard-layouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:15:51 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/keyboard-layouts/</guid>
      <description>My many attempts at creating a more optimal keyboard layout for my self. So far all of the layouts have been used on a normal TKL keyboard, but with the latest layouts the goal has been to create a layout that would work on a Charybdis by Bastard Keyboards. See the cover picture for how the keys have been moved around to make the latest layout work on a normal keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St (simple terminal)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/st/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:06:32 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/st/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;st is a simple terminal implementation for X&amp;rdquo; - suckless.org.
This is my configuration of the suckless terminal st. I have installed a few different patches and made some configuration changes to improve the usability and look of the terminal.
Try My Config To try my configuration on any system with Nix installed run the following:
nix run github:jonwin1/st-jonwin Patches Srollback: Allow scrolling back through the terminal output using keybinds or the mouse wheel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:27:52 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/this-website/</guid>
      <description>I created this website to have a single place to document all my projects and share them. It will also serve as a kind of portfolio that shows what things I have worked on and learned.
This Website This website was build with Hugo which is a open-source static site generator, Hugo allows you to generate posts like this one from markdown files. I use the PaperMod theme for my site, it is a clean and simple theme with many useful features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pictures</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 11:26:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pictures/</guid>
      <description>2024 Rally Sweden Jumping into the Red Barn Arena
My Car My car, a BMW E46 330xi.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
